Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
All my life,
I wanted to be like Omar Sharif.
The romantic lead in all his films.
-Samiha, will you marry me?
-Marry you?
-I want to marry you, Sawsan.
-Auntie, did you hear that?
He expresses his feelings
in a way that melts your heart.
I had to see you,
and be with you,
Here's to another year of love.
All it takes is a word, and she's in love.
I love
you so much.
But… But I'm…
I'm hopeless at expressing my feelings.
Sama!
My self-confidence? Zero.
All because of "the monster."
Sama, how are you?
I came today to confess to you,
and to tell you…
Sama's the most beautiful part of my life.
Come on. Get out!
Lucky me that a girl like her
loves a guy like me.
We're nothing alike.
She's full of life, and she loves life,
while I…
I never thought I'd end up like this.
GROOM & TWO BRIDES
Okay, so the four of us
decided to go, right?
I thought, "Okay, let me check the site
and check out everything
and book tickets."
We went and bought tents,
and bought everything for camping.
So, I went to the website,
But anyways, they let it slide.
What else could they do?
You know what I mean?
Adam, what's wrong?
Ah! Sorry! You brought me here
to tell me something!
Sama, let the man speak!
So, what did you want to say?
Sama, I…
From the first time I saw you, I
I mean, I feel that
that it's time for me to
to tell you that
I've wanted to say it for so long, but…
I love you.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
But I--
Uh, wait. I'm not done yet.
Adam…
Adam! What are you doing?
I'm doing what they do in movies.
Sama, will you marry me?
Ah! Oh!
Adam, sweetie,
I love you so much.
And you're a catch.
But I'm not ready to take this step yet.
I still haven't traveled enough,
I haven't seen the world.
So, I feel I haven't really lived yet,
you know?
And that was the last time
I ever saw Sama.
She traveled in search of a future.
And it was also the last time
I ever saw poor sweet Adam.
THREE YEARS LATER
I decided to go see a psychiatrist
to resolve all the insecurities
"the monster" caused me,
and become an expert on girls.
As for "the monster,"
that's another story.
That's for later. Let's stay on track.
There are a few essentials.
Once you figure them out,
you can land any girl.
Wow!
Thank you, Adam!
Rule number two: as long as she's talking,
please, shut up.
Rule number three.
He's cheating on me!
I caught him cheating!
-Every woman, no matter how pretty…
-I'm so upset!
…someone's cheated on her.
Be kind.
Rule number four: Make her laugh.
But hold on.
Don't think it's that simple
and relationships work out that easily.
No. Of course not.
That's why,
it's absolutely necessary for every guy
to learn rule number five by heart.
In life, you only get one chance.
So you must always be brave,
and go for it.
Rule number five:
Don't be afraid of rejection.
Anyway, men tend to be 20%
more thick-skinned than women.
So, it's fine!
Most importantly, always remember:
People come and go.
Of course,
there's love that won't fade easily.
Sometimes it never does.
Are you for real?
You didn't even ask about rule number one!
Rule number one:
Don't even think about getting attached.
I know I'll regret this decision.
But you and I need to break up.
I have a chronic, incurable illness.
No!
Take it easy.
I mean, if it were up to me,
I do want you.
But my parents don't approve.
Honestly, I quit my job,
and I'm going back to Kuwait.
I'm in debt.
I might go to prison.
And if you find yourself
in a difficult situation,
and you don't know which rule to follow,
run!
Adam, you pathetic loser!
You're absolute garbage!
And this is Sarah.
But there's no time
to tell you about Sarah,
because she's not even
the star of this film.
Everything you asked for
in the meeting is ready.
I sent you all the files
and I sent you the offers.
One more thing.
I asked for Mr. Jabir's permission.
I told him you just got back,
and need to rest, yeah?
Good.
He insisted on seeing you today,
but I said, "That's not possible."
-"He needs to rest."
-Tomorrow, then.
I get it. He owns a business,
and needs to settle stuff with you today,
but I explained it to him.
-"You know Adam. He has to rest--"
-Talal, enough. Come on.
Sorry, forgive me.
Welcome back.
Hey, Talal.
I'm having trouble with the lock.
-No clue. It won't open.
-Wait, what?
-What do you mean it won't?
-Do you have…
Okay, hang on.
I might know someone who can help.
Let me check my phone.
One of the guys had a similar problem,
and I hooked him up. Let me--
Hello? Adam, are you there?
Adam!
Azzam? What are you doing in my house?
Hello? Adam!
Hi, Mr. Jabir. How are you?
How's everything?
I just called Talal.
I told him I'd call you today
to… meet you.
I wasn't waiting till tomorrow.
But look at that. You're here.
I come into the house, and here you are.
Would you like some tea?
Or have you had some?
It's okay. Make yourselves at home.
Do you know how hard I worked
to build this company?
And I won't allow anyone,
whoever they are,
to ruin what I've built!
-Uh, Mr. Jabir, I know that.
-Shh!
Yes, sir.
I heard about the planned theft
at the company.
-Yes, but, Mr. Jabir, I--
-Shut up! Let me finish!
Yes, sir.
I also learned that you…
were the one
who stopped that from happening.
Your late father was my friend
since before you were born.
I know you were raised on values.
I'll make you an offer
you cannot refuse.
Sign.
But what am I going to sign?
Sign!
Here.
Congratulations.
Thank you!
You are now officially
my business partner,
not just an employee.
Frankly, I can't think of anyone else
who'd look out for this company,
and take it to even higher places
after I'm gone.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything.
Just promise me you'll take good care
of both the company and my daughter.
I promise. Don't worry.
Your daughter?
Yes, my daughter, Yasmine.
You'll get married.
Congratulations.
Your daughter, Yasmine?
No, seriously. Am I dreaming or what?
I mean, I can't belie… I'd be honored…
I'd be honored to marry Yasmine.
It'd be my honor to be your in-law
and be welcomed into your home.
It's just that I think--
It'd be unfair to Yasmine.
She deserves someone better.
And I'm sure she'll find someone.
But, I mean, I'm really proud of myself.
It means a lot that,
out of all people, you picked me.
But I have to say no.
You're saying no to me?
You said no to him?
Of course I didn't say no to him!
What more could you ask for?
A bride, a fortune, and a company.
Talal, please, shut up.
I'm not marrying her.
I won't even go see her.
I'll make up some excuse.
I'll tell him
I have a chronic illness or whatever!
Do you know who Yasmine is?
She's "the monster"!
Sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm done.
Suppose I went to see her,
and she wasn't my type.
What if she hasn't changed?
What am I supposed to tell Jabir?
"I don't want to marry your daughter"?
"I don't want her"?
Besides, come here.
You want me to leave all the other girls
and get married?
You want me to settle down
and keep things proper? No!
I won't even go see her!
MR. JABIR
Hi, Mr. Jabir.
You told her that I'll see her?
Adam!
Of course I want to see her.
Your wish is my command.
Your wish is my command!
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
Where's Yasmine?
Sorry I'm late.
I got held up at the office.
But I'm usually very punctual.
Wow, you haven't changed.
I… I mean, you're a beauty.
The last time we met, I was seven, right?
You used to kick me around like a ball.
You still remember?
Such things--
Thank you, Salwa. Good job.
I'm the wedding planner, not the chef.
I don't blame you.
You all thought I'd be a chef
because I loved food.
Don't exaggerate.
Oh!
You still pack a punch.
And you're still a softie.
-I'm not a softie.
-"I'm not a softie."
You haven't changed one bit.
I know you inside out. Wait.
You still think you can sing?
Do you still record yourself singing
on tapes and hide them?
No.
Oh my God! Those were the days!
But…
Anyway, I'm very happy for you.
But, Yasmine, let me tell you something.
When I signed the contract,
I didn't know it had this condition.
But I signed it.
I don't get it. What did you sign?
Why are you happy for me?
Dad told me you're here about the wedding.
Dad, you told me he was coming
for a wedding, didn't you?
-I did, dear. Correct.
-Yes, for a wedding, not our wedding!
-Don't be stubborn.
-Why are you interfering? Please!
Just let me choose the right man
at the right time!
Dear, I just want the joy
of seeing you as a bride.
Promise me you'll give him a chance.
It's settled then. You promised.
Dad, Dad… Dad?
Dad.
Good job, everyone.
"The monster" turned out to be… cute.
Mr. Jabir will be pleased,
I get to have a beautiful bride,
and be a business owner.
So, I'll be living the sweet life.
What more could I ask for?
Now, the plan is simple.
This time, nothing can stand in my way.
Except if Sama comes back suddenly.
Seeing her reminded me
of how much I love her
and how hard she is to forget.
Tell the DJ to turn it down.
The bride's tossing the bouquet.
Come on, tell me more.
It's cute that he's trying
to find you a groom.
Hala, focus. This is a huge wedding.
If you get me his zodiac sign,
I'll give you a perfect read on him.
A long time ago, I met a Libra.
We were a total mismatch.
So, what's his sign?
Who cares about his sign?
I don't need anyone to make me happy.
-You know why?
-Why?
Because I make my own happiness.
I don't even get why people marry.
Oh, dear God!
You do know what you do
for a living, right?
What?
My life's one thing, my job's another.
I keep telling you.
We keep feelings out of the job.
Do you even have feelings
to let them interfere with work?
I've never met someone who can't cry.
Never a tear, never moved by anything.
What's wrong with you?
Yes, that's me!
Answer me this:
Ever seen a couple who are always happy?
-It doesn't exist.
-Yes.
-Of course it exists!
-That's a lie!
It's our nature to lie to ourselves.
Just so we can keep going.
There's no such thing as love.
Trust me, the minute you fall in love,
they break your heart and ruin your life.
Okay, Yasmine, look.
Watch! Look.
Look how happy her friends are for her.
They're celebrating love.
You know what they'll do
once they get home?
-What?
-They'll all hop on a conference call.
They'll gossip about the bride,
the wedding, her dress
the food, and even her family will--
Yeah, okay! That's enough, I get it.
Look how cute her mother is!
Look how emotional she is!
She's happy
she can turn her empty room into a gym.
Unbelievable! Shed that tear already!
Come on. Shed it!
You're in the most emotional line of work!
What are you, a crocodile?
A statue? Feel something. Cry!
-Just accept it!
-Gather around.
-The bride's about to throw the bouquet.
-I'm not made for marriage!
Sama's back!
My life is ruined!
I'm done for!
You know what it's like to have two?
Two women, Tala. Two.
One's the love of my life,
the other's the monster
who holds my future.
Want me to shock you even more?
I want to shock you.
Tomorrow, they both want to meet me!
Hey, listen to me! I need your help!
Watch Sama.
Don't let her leave the hotel tomorrow
no matter what.
If she sees me with another woman,
I'm done for.
Do whatever you can to distract her.
I told her I'm going to meet her
in the lobby at six sharp.
Got it?
If anyone knows what women want, it's me.
I know how they think,
how to make them get attached.
But this time around,
I decided to do the opposite.
Hey, Talal. What's the situation?
The plan is to make "the monster"
decide to run away.
Great! Everything is going great!
Please, I'm counting on you guys
to have everything ready
by six o'clock, okay?
-And I need a taxi, please.
-Nobody leaves the hotel.
The heat is deadly.
Plan number one:
Take her somewhere
that makes you look intellectual and cool.
I never thought you liked museums.
I don't like museums!
Then, embarrass and shock her.
PLAN NUMBER TWO
You embarrassed us!
Insult her femininity indirectly.
Make her feel
she needs to work on her body.
How about we go have some burgers?
Unless you're on a diet.
Honestly, I wouldn't blame you!
What a softie!
Sure, let's have some burgers. Why not?
Don't eat it!
Ma'am.
How about we treat you
to one of our amenities
which I'm sure you'll love?
No, thank you. Not interested.
Trust me!
I'm sure you're going to love this offer.
Besides, ma'am, why would you go out
in that scorching heat?
I'm going to surprise my fiancé at work.
You can't, ma'am. You can't.
You can't leave the hotel, please!
Why not?
Uh, why not?
Because… your face… looks tired.
-My face looks tired?
-And your skin looks withered.
And you want to go out
in that flaming hot weather?
You know?
Then end it with the knockout.
The bill.
He let you pay?
-Hey, watch out!
-What? Oh, no! I spilled the coffee.
Yes.
He let me pay. So what?
What do you mean, "Yes"?
How could you even accept that?
What an idiot! He's so stingy!
I can't believe it!
Have gentlemen gone extinct?
I told you to get me his zodiac sign.
I'll tell you what it is.
In my estimation,
he must be either a Taurus or an Aries.
But judging by his aura,
he's most probably… a Taurus.
Please, ask him for…
Hey! Yasmine, where's your head at?
-You know what this means?
-No. What?
He doesn't have hang-ups
about gender roles.
He believes a woman
doesn't need anyone to complete her,
or to pay for her to then own her
and have her wrapped around his finger
just because he picked up a check.
No.
He's different. He's…
I felt he was secure in his manhood,
and I felt that he respected me
as a strong, independent woman.
He wasn't like that when we were little.
He's mature now.
Mature. He's different.
So different.
Nice.
I know what will happen next.
-I'll run away!
-You'll call him!
-You'll run away?
-Yes!
You'll run away again?
Yasmine, why do you run every time
you like someone? I don't get it.
Why don't you ever allow yourself
to experience love?
Love is so wonderful.
Experience how it feels to…
Wait a minute. Did you say…?
You think I like him?
No, I was just saying he's matured,
but, like him? Me? No!
Of course you don't.
God forbid, that's not what I meant.
I meant,
why don't you give yourself… a chance?
Maybe, just maybe, in the future,
you'll like him.
No.
Damn you! Where are you going?
Where are you going?
Okay, if not for yourself,
do it for your father.
I'm not calling him!
Don't call him!
Yes, run away!
I hate you!
I'll come slap you
right after I clean up the coffee.
Stay calm.
-Stay calm.
-Stop.
Rub the avocado all over your face.
Let it seep into every pore.
-Talal!
-Lots of water for--
Talal, what are you doing? Who's this?
Uh…
Oh! You know each other?
Sa… Sama!
Uh… He's my cousin!
-Ah!
-Yeah. I'm his cousin.
Uh, my cousin, he works for me…
-Uh…
-He works with me.
And he also works here in the hotel.
He's into oils and avocado.
Uh, I work in cosmetics.
I've been very successful.
It's all thanks to my late grandma.
She always encouraged me.
Never mind that right now. He's my cousin.
-Talal, you may leave. Thanks.
-Right.
Like I said,
if you ever need an ice bath, or…
-Talal! Go ahead.
-Call me.
Stay calm, drink green tea,
and what did I teach you to say?
Eat this. It's good for the stomach.
Sorry, Adam.
I didn't want things to be like this.
I had a whole plan in mind!
No, baby! Don't worry about it.
Don't worry at all.
I'm actually thinking
we should cancel everything today.
I mean, it's been a long day
for both you and I.
And tomorrow is a new day, a new slate.
So, you and I will be alone,
just the two of us.
No third wheel.
Okay, at least,
I'll look cleaner and nicer.
-Not green.
-It's okay.
Don't worry.
I'll go now, okay?
No, please, Adam.
Let me fix a mistake I made years ago.
Sure, I've said Sama's impulsive
and a little crazy, but…
I never thought she'd do this.
Let me be crazy now,
because I might never do this again, so…
Sama! No. Sa--
I might never find someone
who'd wait for me all these years,
stay faithful to me,
and never even think
about loving someone else while I'm away.
Because he's sure about our love.
What are you doing? Come on!
Adam, I could search the whole world
and never find anyone like you.
We're meant for each other.
Adam Saleh,
will you marry me?
Hey, Adam!
You said "Yes"? What's wrong with you?
Adam, call her right now
and call it off, please.
And say what?
I don't know. "The ceiling caved in."
"I hit my head,"
or "I lost my mind, and now I'm crazy."
Sorry.
Adam, can you call her
and call it off, please? Now!
Will you calm down
and listen to me instead?
No! You listen to me.
I swear, you're driving me nuts.
Do you know
what my late grandma used to say?
If you bake bread and mess it up,
you eat it. And if you dig a hole for--
What? What are you rambling about?
Don't argue, Adam.
Please, call her now, for God's sake!
Talal, buddy.
Calm down, relax. Listen to me.
Go ahead.
I actually managed
to make Yasmine hate me.
After what happened today,
she's going to call her dad and say,
"I don't want this guy."
And how will he respond?
He'll respect her decision.
That way it's not my fault.
It's her choice.
You know what I think?
I got rid of Yasmine,
and Sama had no idea.
So, today, I can marry Sama. High five!
I swear, you're going to give me a stroke.
Hear me out, Mr. Mastermind.
This is Yasmine.
A hot bombshell
that can't be missed out on.
And who's this guy?
This is our genius Adam.
Now, good ol' Adam
is attracted to Yasmine.
This is where the story gets juicy, why?
Because Adam is marrying Sama!
Explain that, Mr. Genius!
Buddy.
Yasmine, I've already driven her away.
She's gone!
And that's where the film ends!
Hello?
This is Yasmine.
Hey, Yasmine.
I had a great time yesterday.
What… You had a great time?
Yes. I did.
So, how about, if you've got no plans,
and I mean definitely no plans,
we go out today?
I'm proud of you.
I'm so proud of you!
Just to be clear, we're…
we're just friends, okay?
Then why did you want to see me?
For…
For my father.
Stunning.
Welcome, sir. Here you go.
Welcome, ma'am. Here you go.
A move called "Pizza on ice"…
I like traveling, I like art…
You know what?
I want you to try this. It's delicious.
Right?
So, you want to spend your life
bouncing between women?
-Of course not!
-So?
My thing with Yasmin isn't gonna happen.
Okay.
Any plans for tomorrow?
Yeah. No, don't worry, I'm--
Sama's in bed.
Yes.
Oh! No!
Come here.
What you're doing right now
is the biggest mistake. Man…
Think. Make a decision.
Choose Sama or Yasmine!
Yasmine or Sama!
But if you keep messing around,
it'll end in disaster.
Be clear and honest with them!
Did you ever think what would happen
if they found out
you've been playing them both?
Do you know what my late grandma
used to say?
I know. But I'm telling you,
once we have the wedding, it'll be fine.
-Just do this.
-Arm in arm?
-Slowly. Yeah.
-Yes. Like this.
No. Hold on.
No. Hold on a second. No! It's not--
Slowly.
Okay, wait.
-Come on. Help me out.
-Hold out your arm.
I want you to hold his arm
like he's your rock.
I need your eyes full
of love and affection…
Hey, Yasmine!
Hey… Hey, what's wrong?
-Where are you running away to?
-I don't know!
-I don't know what I'm feeling.
-You like her?
Of course not!
He's just fun to be with!
She makes me laugh without meaning to.
He's tender.
She listens to me.
Looks like you like him
Looks like you're in love with him
You're going to marry him
-I'll get to be a bridesmaid
-No!
We're just friends.
Nothing more.
I'm very pleased and happy.
When you were kids,
your late father and I would say,
"Cute! These two are meant
for each other."
"They'll get married one day, hopefully."
Your late parents, and your late mother,
they would've been so happy.
They'd say exactly what I'm saying.
I'm very pleased.
But hey!
People are talking.
You're together all the time.
I can't have that.
I care about my daughter's reputation,
and my son-in-law's,
who I love just as much.
But, sir--
I'm not finished!
Besides,
I have a surprise for you.
Six weeks from today
is your wedding day!
The first of next month.
And I don't want you guys
worrying about a thing!
But, Mr. Jabir--
Mr. Jabir…
It's an honor.
It's an honor to marry your daughter.
Yasmine, wait! Let's talk, Yasmine!
I thought it was okay!
I thought you were happy!
Happy?
I'm happy that… I don't know,
that we're just friends, nothing more.
You expect me to say,
"I don't want your daughter"?
Are you for real?
Well, I don't know, maybe…
Maybe you could be a man,
and face my father,
and say, "Yasmine and I are just friends"?
Now I get it!
You and my father set me up!
You planned this together, right?
You…
I figured by now
you'd have some character,
but you're still clueless
and lack any character!
-I lack character?
-Yes!
Because I didn't want to hurt your father?
Because I saw how excited he was?
Because I saw you happy for a whole week?
How can you even be okay
with hurting your father?
He's your father!
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I have no character.
But you haven't changed.
You're still a monster!
I'm a monster?
I'm a monster? Adam, come here!
I'm not cold-hearted,
and I have a conscience!
I'm his daughter,
I can't break his heart. You talk to him!
You talk to him. You say no to him.
I've never seen him this happy!
You tell… Adam, stop!
I'm talking to you, stop!
What's the solution? Now what?
It's simple,
and the plan is straightforward.
You and I will make a deal,
and pretend we're engaged.
We'll just play along.
Yeah, and in six weeks,
we get married to play along.
Wow, what a great game. It's so much fun.
Wait… Uh, Adam!
Fine, go ahead. Sorry. I'll hear you out.
Our engagement will be fake.
We'll make him think
we're having constant problems.
That way, he'll believe
we can't possibly stay together.
He wouldn't want his daughter to be sad,
unhappy, and crying all the time.
He'll be the one to call it off.
Not either of us.
What's with you guys?
So, you and I… are just friends.
Of course we are.
Then, promise me that no matter what,
you won't get attached.
You promise me you won't get attached.
-"A monster"?
-Not now.
What are you doing here?
How did you get in?
Your cousin gave me the key.
Didn't he see you coming in?
-Adam, you're not supposed to be here!
-Hold on.
Is anyone else here?
Did you see anyone?
What do you mean?
Why? Are you expecting someone?
No. It's just that I hold meetings here.
My business meetings.
-Why did you lock the door?
-It's safer this way.
Yeah!
Lately, I've been all about surprises!
Surprise after surprise
after surprise after…
Lately, I've been sensing
that you're very tired
and not eating healthy.
So, I decided to cook you some food,
and packed it in a Tupperware
in the fridge.
This way, you'll have meals
to take to work all week.
But you weren't supposed to be here!
I also left you a little note
on the piano!
I don't even know why you have one.
You know, you're the best.
You surprised me.
Really?
No one's cared for me like this in ages.
It's because I've been working on myself
to become the best wife in the world.
I want to do everything you like.
I hate seeing you so worn out.
But I don't know
if I deserve this much love.
You're the one who deserves it the most.
I don't know how to dance!
That's okay.
Honey, can I ask you something
without you thinking I'm crazy?
Ask away. I'd never think that.
Is it possible that one day,
you'd marry another woman?
I know Sharia allows four wives,
but would you do it?
Okay, not four. Let's just say two.
Would you do it or not?
Did Talal say something to you?
What does Talal have to do with anything?
I'm asking you?
I've been thinking about this for a while
because my friend's husband
married another woman.
Is it possible that one day
you'd do that to me?
No way.
Me, marry four women?
No. That's very, very unlikely.
Four?
Maybe two.
Silly you! Of course you wouldn't!
Suppose I did it, what would you do?
I'll grab her by the hair,
and I'll beat her up so bad.
-Then I'll rub her face on the floor!
-Easy.
Are you sure you and Talal didn't talk?
A little.
Open the fridge.
I cooked you a meal.
Your meal will be ready every day
when you get home from work.
Remember how much I love you.
I'll love you more and more every day.
BEST WEDDING PLANNER IN KUWAIT
YASMINE ABDULLAH
-Hey, Yasmine.
-Adam, I don't get how you're so calm.
I don't know. I don't get it.
How are you? How's everything?
How are you not worried?
Haven't you seen
the wedding venues photos Dad sent?
I'll be there in 30 minutes.
We need to start a fight in front of him.
We've got to get him
to believe this isn't working.
-Adam, I'm so done!
-Okay, I'll be here.
Guess who's stopping by the office?
-Who?
-Your fiancée.
Wow, she's quick.
Good morning!
Sama!
How are you? Don't tell me
you and Talal planned this too.
Welcome. Please come in.
-Uh… Give me a minute.
-Yeah.
It's surprise season these days.
Yasmine is on her way here.
-Talal! I have a question!
-I'll get back to you later!
Mr. Adam's in a meeting
with an important client.
If anyone asks, he's not here. Okay?
Yes.
God help us.
Uh… Miss Yasmine!
Hi. Hi, Talal. Good to see you.
How are you?
I'm good…
Talal?
Talal.
Talal, Hala.
Hala, Talal.
Hala. It's good to meet you.
Hello.
I'm so sorry.
Mr. "Office"…
Uh, Mr. Adam is in his office.
He's in an important meeting.
With the Chinese delegation.
He asked me to have you wait
in the conference room.
Yeah. Please.
This way. Welcome.
What is it with you and pianos?
I mean, do you like them?
I told you, I've always played the piano.
I don't remember you telling me.
Maybe I wasn't paying attention.
I can picture you playing and singing.
Sama, uh…
You know what?
Why don't we just go to a restaurant?
Wait! What about the food I made you?
-Adam, don't tell me you forgot it.
-The food?
No. The food is right here. Look.
The official sponsor, no less,
is waiting for you
in the conference room, Mr. Adam.
No less?
I saw him.
The meeting! Sorry, honey.
I forgot I had a meeting.
Uh… The "selficial" sponsor himself?
"Official," Mr. Adam.
"Official."
I have to go. You stay here.
-I'll be right back.
-Yeah, I'll wait.
-The "selficial" sponsor?
-"Official"!
Right, "official."
Adam. Adam!
One of these days
you'll give me a heart attack.
Go.
Sorry, a meeting came up.
Yes, but I’d like to resolve
the photos now.
Let me finish the meeting
so I can focus on that.
Fine. Okay.
But can you finish it quick?
I'm starving and I feel dizzy,
so I want to go eat.
You're starving? Food? I have my food.
I'll go get it. Just stay here.
Don't move.
I'll go get you the food. Okay?
Fine, okay.
Talal, come with me.
Hello, Mr. Jabir.
Simon, the jeweler, is on his way
to the office,
so Yasmine can choose a wedding ring.
But hey!
I want her to think it was your idea.
Of course, I understand.
Talal.
Listen, the jeweler is coming.
When he gets here,
take him to Yasmine's conference room.
The conference room.
Uh, Talal!
What?
Make one mistake,
and Sama is your responsibility.
It's all the same!
You're my responsibility, and her too.
-Same thing.
-Be quiet, not now.
Don't mess this up.
-Hey, where to?
-I'm going to the toilet.
Uh… Can't you just hold it?
I mean, let me show you the way. Come on.
Hello there!
Hi!
-Greetings to the family!
-What did he say?
Don't mind him. He's crazy. Come.
The restroom is this way. Don't get lost.
It's okay. I got it.
-No, it's fine. Right here.
-Okay.
-I'll wait for you here, okay?
Excuse me, sorry.
Do you know where Adam is?
Yes, Mr. Adam was just here.
Where are you going?
I'm hungry. I'll go while you finish up.
-No. I'm done with the meeting.
-You're done?
Yes. Uh… Come on, let's go to my office.
Okay.
-I'll be right behind you, okay?
-Yeah, okay.
Talal!
Listen.
When Sama comes out,
take her to the conference room.
The conference room.
You still remember I like yellow roses?
How could I forget?
Hey, can you call my dad
and put him on speaker?
Why?
It's time we started arguing
in front of him, like we planned.
Imagine, Adam,
my dad is planning a huge wedding,
and he wants to invite our family,
our friends, our acquaintances.
I'm not sure if he's sent the invites.
He's booking flights
for the ones abroad. Imagine that!
Okay, relax. What's gotten into you?
You know what?
Eat so you won't have a meltdown.
I'll call him.
Hello, Mr. Jabir.
Yasmine's here, and you're on speaker.
Right. Did she see the, uh…
No, Mr. Jabir, uh…
Yasmine has something to say.
Dad?
What you sent is gorgeous.
I mean, I like them all so much,
but Adam says your taste sucks.
What? No, Mr. Jabir. I never said that.
I don't know what's with Yasmine.
What do you mean? Am I a liar?
He's been saying this all along.
Imagine what that could lead to.
Adam, our tastes
couldn't be more different.
Uncle, do you hear
how she's talking to me?
As if she had taste!
This is perfectly normal, dear.
Every couple about to marry
has these little spats.
He says one thing, she says another.
This is all normal, you know?
Just leave everything to me.
Now what?
I don't know, but, uh…
Let's just keep arguing in front of him.
But, Adam, do me a favor.
Never ever cook again!
What's your zodiac sign?
-Talal. Mr. Simon, the jeweler.
-Mr. Simon!
Hello! Look at you,
you gorgeous, beautiful thing!
Thank you. That's very kind of you.
Mr. Adam will see you in a bit.
Just a few seconds.
Wait in the conference room.
-Thank you!
-It's to your right. Thank you.
What a beauty!
Mr. Simon, to your right if you please!
Go ahead, thank you.
I'm an Aries.
Hello, bride-to-be!
How did you know?
We haven't told anyone.
I'm here today just for you.
And I brought you a collection
you'll hopefully like.
Don't worry.
Whatever piece you like,
it'll be ready by the first of the month.
-We'll meet tonight, okay?
-Okay.
-Oh! I forgot my phone!
-Here in my office?
No, in the conference room.
No. Stay here! I'll get it!
-Why?
-I don't mind.
-No, it's okay. I'll get it.
-Just wait here.
-I don't like this attitude.
-But--
I said I'll get it. Stop it.
What's this?
I don't know who called me
a million times.
Hello?
Hi. Yes.
This is Yasmine. Go ahead?
Yes, sure. No problem.
Is tomorrow okay?
Oh, okay. Today?
Okay. Send me a location
and I'll come to meet you. Good. Okay.
Bye.
That was a bride
who insists on meeting me today.
-I'll go see her, then come to you.
-See you tomorrow… I mean, tonight.
Okay. Bye.
-Where have you been?
-With Simon.
He said the bride finally picked a ring.
What bride?
Yasmine has already left.
I don't get it. You got a call?
No, she called me nonstop,
and insisted we meet today.
Yeah, but why?
I was at a bridal gown shop.
That's why I'm late.
No worries.
-Sama.
-Yasmine.
What's your plan? What's the solution?
-There's only one solution.
-What is it?
-I'll marry Yasmine.
-Okay.
I'll marry Yasmine.
-And Sama.
-Excuse me?
Yeah, why not?
Sharia allows four wives!
Damn you!
You can't even handle one.
How can you be fair with two?
I did a search
on the best wedding planners in Kuwait…
Needless to say…
It's so neat, you know what I mean?
Not like classic weddings.
And I love it. I really love your work.
You're a sweetheart.
That's very kind of you. Thank you.
Uh… are you married?
No, I'm not married.
Okay! My wedding date
is the first of next month.
Sweetie, you'll have to forgive us.
We won't be able to plan it.
No, our thing will be cancelled.
It's a very important event.
Why? No, it's okay.
No, we can't cancel it.
Yes, we'll cancel it.
It's nothing important.
Please, don't tell me
you're not available on that date.
I don't want anyone but you
to plan my wedding.
No.
I do have something, but I'll cancel.
It's not that important.
And I found out the wedding date
by accident. Can you imagine?
He still thinks I don't know.
Okay. So, where's the wedding venue?
Actually, I don't know.
I'm only asking
because we don't have much time.
I need the guest count, and the venue.
So I can organize quickly.
And there's one more thing
if you want the schedule just right.
Are you traveling the same night
for the honeymoon?
The honeymoon.
Yes, the honeymoon, yes!
I'll ask him to take me
to several countries, yes! Oh!
The honeymoon.
Yes.
I'll ask him to take me to…
What's your zodiac sign?
Where were you?
I keep calling you. I got worried.
What are you doing here? Come in.
Did anyone see you?
No, but I called Talal.
He said you were upset and sick,
so I came to check on you.
Glad he didn't give you a key too.
I got you dinner.
I figured I'd join you since you're sick.
Are you crazy? Dinner?
I can't believe you came.
Oh my God! I didn't tell you yet
about that crazy client I met today!
She's totally hyper!
She's a nutcase!
She talks nonstop! Can you imagine?
I have to meet her fiancé
to warn him before he's stuck with her.
Wow!
I have a question before I let you eat.
Okay, shoot.
"A monster"?
Look, that's an old story,
and I'm tired and hungry.
No!
I won't let you eat before you answer.
Believe me,
we don't need to talk about it.
Answer me.
We were kids, so what's done is done.
We're adults now.
I'm sorry I even brought it up.
-Excuse me?
-Look, I'm starving. Can I eat?
You've been calling me "a monster"
since we were kids?
When we were kids,
you used to hit me all the time.
You ate my food, even my French fries.
Don't I love French fries?
Yeah? So?
You used to eat it all.
Fries? Because of fries?
I mean, you call me "a monster"?
Trust me, it's not about fries.
You used to hit me, playfully maybe,
but you packed a punch.
Your personality was stronger than mine.
-That gave me insecurities.
-Insecurities?
Look, I'm bad at expressing myself.
Not insecurities. No.
How do I put this?
You made me doubt myself.
I had no self-confidence.
I used to sing, remember?
You'd make fun of me, and laugh at me.
So, I lost my self-confidence.
I quit singing.
But it's fine! Life goes on!
I don't know… I don't know what to say,
but I'm so sorry.
You think saying "sorry"
will fix the past?
I said it's fine. No problem.
Call now to book your dream honeymoon…
-Adam?
-…in the most beautiful places on earth.
Sweetie, where are we going
for our honeymoon?
Honestly, Sama,
I don't think I can travel right now.
So we're getting married,
and having a wedding,
but no honeymoon trip?
We're just staying home?
Whoa! Oh my goodness! You look…
Right? I really love this one.
I like it because it's narrow
at the waist.
Yes!
Excuse me?
Why is your name on top on both invites?
I'm the man.
The man's name should be first.
I'm a wedding planner. None of my invites…
-Uncle, why are you silent? Help me out.
-Dad, see?
They're really, really huge, so that…
What's wrong?
-Aw! It's beautiful!
-Dear God!
-Please!
-Hala, please, let's go!
Let's see.
She said it, God rest her soul.
My grandma said it.
-What did she say?
-No man can serve two masters.
Okay, so about the colors,
I want bright, happy ones, you know?
-Yes.
-So when people walk in,
they're surrounded by color and feel joy.
Wouldn't it be better
to stick to two colors so it's not too--
No! Not at all.
Hello? Hey, sweetie, where are you?
So, you'll be late today?
Am I not going to see you?
Bye.
Why doesn't he ever come with you?
I haven't told him
I hired a wedding planner.
This is a surprise,
just like the wedding is.
Okay, but what matters is,
are you two compatible? Same taste? Alike?
Absolutely not! We have nothing in common.
I like traveling,
having fun, and doing crazy things.
He's a homebody.
He only goes out occasionally just for me.
Like, I'm here, and he's here.
Oh, wow!
I couldn't be with someone so different.
I feel like I need someone like me.
In everything.
Our interests have to be the same.
I mean, this is marriage.
I mean, like, marriage is…
Marriage is…
Marriage is forever.
Yes!
Yes, but wait.
I could be wrong,
and you could be right because…
because people
don't always have to be compatible.
Because if they're not--
Maybe if we're not,
I'll miss out on the things I love.
No. If they're not compatible,
they'll bring the best
out of each other, right?
What's wrong? I'm worried.
I'm already where you…
"The monster" wants to make amends.
Come on.
Here you go, Mr. Adam.
Give me your plate.
Let me serve you.
There you go.
You're right.
I know saying "sorry"
doesn't fix the past,
but I thought I'd try.
Okay, I have a question.
How did I give you all these insecurities?
I mean, you are…
I mean, you're fine.
You're… successful, and…
I mean, and handsome.
You think I'm handsome?
I mean,
you could say I worked on myself,
and tried to change.
I dated a lot of girls,
just to rebuild my confidence.
Mm, a lot? Like, how many is "a lot"?
Like, a lot.
-A lot.
-And why didn't they stay with you?
They couldn't put up with you?
Well, actually, there's one.
Yes, and?
I fell in love with her,
and I proposed to her.
Yes? And? What happened next?
Finish the story!
She said…
She said no.
After I proposed to her
like they do in the movies,
and presented the ring,
and got down on one knee.
She said,
"I want to live my life,"
then she moved out of the country.
But let's assume this:
She comes back to you
and says, "I'm sorry, forgive me."
"But now, I love you,
and I want to get back with you."
Would you take her back?
Your turn.
Ask.
Honestly, I don't know.
Tell me something
I don't know about you. Something weird.
Anything.
I don't know what to say.
I can't think of anything.
I don't know.
Did you know that I can't cry?
What do you mean?
I don't tear up.
No matter what happens, or how upset I am.
I never cry.
Wait a second.
When was the last time?
You know what?
I'll get us something to drink.
Wait, Yasmine. It's fine.
Just tell me the last time you cried.
I answered you.
-You have to. Okay, don't.
-I don't want to. I want to go…
-When was the last time you cried?
-Please, Adam, let…
When my mother died!
Happy now?
The last time I cried
was when my mother died.
Thank you for what you did here.
You've done more than enough.
Thanks a lot.
-One more thing.
-What?
-The big surprise.
-More surprises?
-Sit still.
-No, tell me. I hate surprises.
Please, Adam! Don't ruin it!
I've been planning this a long time.
-Okay.
-Hold on.
-Okay, I'm waiting.
-Just a second!
You're nuts. What are you doing?
Adam. Please, sing with me.
No, I don't sing anymore!
-I'm not singing! You sing!
-Please, for me!
-I gave you this insecurity, please.
-Go on.
God, you're so funny. I love you.
What did you say?
Nothing.
That's it, I can't keep lying
to both of them anymore.
The problem is they're both great,
but I'm exhausted!
Congrats!
You finally realized! Great!
Anyway. I kept telling you
that my late grandma--
For God's sake!
Not now.
I'm dying here, I don't know what to do.
I know it's my fault, I know.
But I was torn between the love of my life
and "the monster."
It turns out she isn't a monster at all.
She listens to me.
She brings out feelings
I never had before.
I mean, she makes me feel alive.
But at the same, I mean, Sama…
She's my first love.
I never imagined she'd love me back.
I used to dream of marrying her.
But at the same time,
Yasmine and I are so compatible.
But I don't know.
I still love Sama very much.
What did that woman you adore do
when she decided she hadn't lived enough?
-She walked out on you, right?
-I know!
That's exactly why
I don't want her to suffer like I did!
What to do?
I don't know what to do.
I've got it. Just love him back.
No! I never wanted anything!
-I don't want this, but--
-Why not?
Because when I'm with him,
he listens to me, accepts me.
And when he calls,
and I see his name on my phone…
-Yes?
-My heart jumps! I don't know!
Well, this is nice!
-No! It's wrong!
-Why?
Because it shouldn't happen.
Huh? I don't understand.
Where's the problem?
I did the one thing she told me not to.
I promised him not to do that either.
What have you done this time?
Wait! What… What have you done?
-I got attached.
I'll fix this.
It's time I tell Sama the truth
and end this.
I can't let myself hurt her.
Excuse me.
Sama. I'm here for Sama.
I just want to talk to her.
Sorry. Sama!
What are you doing here? You're nuts!
Come on! I need to talk to you!
Can't hear you! The music's too loud!
I need to talk to you!
I can't hear you in here!
It's too loud!
Sama, you and I are…
Come with me!
Yasmine, answer the phone.
I caught you, Adam!
Mr. Jabir, just let me explain.
Explain what?
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
I was about to fix everything.
You should've told me!
Not put me in this tricky situation!
I was afraid you'd misunderstand.
Why would I misunderstand?
Plus, you're marrying my daughter.
You should've said,
"Uncle Jabir, give me the key."
Not change the lock
and have me waiting outside every day!
Come. Sit down.
Dear God! What's this?
What have you done to yourself?
You're covered in colors.
-What happened?
-It's a long story.
A long story?
Honestly, son, I'm here to thank you.
For what you did.
It's impressive, honestly.
You fixed what I messed up.
And I'm proud of you.
Has she told you
why she was against marriage?
After her mother passed away,
she saw how much I suffered,
and how much losing her mother
broke my heart.
She decided
never to risk having her heart broken
over someone she loves.
She convinced herself people…
…people come and go.
And frankly, son,
this is the first time
I've seen my daughter this happy.
Look here!
I'm warning you! If you ever upset her…
Sorry, but I don't know where he's gone!
It's okay. Don't worry.
I'll see him tomorrow
and get to know him. It's okay.
Now, you…
Tell me, how are you feeling?
Are you ready?
It's okay. Don't worry. I mean,
everyone gets nervous
a day before their wedding.
It's a big decision.
I bet he's nervous too.
You both have separate lives
that'll become one. So--
Exactly what I've been thinking.
Later I won't be able to go where I want,
or do what I want.
Then there'll be kids,
they'll grow up,
which is more responsibility.
-I have to help them study--
-Stop! Sama!
-Life is… Oh!
-Sama!
I promise everything will be fine, okay?
But I don't know whether I'm ready or not!
Well, you have to know.
Because now you have time.
Later on, you won't.
You have to know if you love him or not.
The thing is, I can't leave Adam.
Adam is amazing.
His name is Adam?
Yes! And he loves me so much!
He proposed to me in public
at a restaurant, and I said no!
And on top of all that,
after I came back to Kuwait,
I found out he never dated again,
and waited for me.
How can I leave him? It'd devastate him.
Can I see Adam's picture?
Yeah.
He's amazing, right?
Yasmine, are you okay?
Hi, Sama. How are you?
I need to see you tomorrow, okay?
Sama, I have to tell you something.
No, Adam.
No, Adam. I'm the one who has to tell you.
Adam, I love you so much.
I love you so much.
You're the love of my life.
But…
I don't think I can take it anymore.
I came back to you
because I missed you so much.
I said to myself,
"Sama, enough. You need to get serious."
"It's time to grow up,
settle down, and quit this nonsense."
And I didn't want to do that
with anyone but you.
Adam, I love you so much.
But I'm not ready to
have kids and start a family.
I felt like it scared me
and weighed on me a lot.
I don't feel ready yet.
I still want to travel and see the world.
Adam, please don't cry. Please!
Please, don't make it any harder.
I'm already having a hard time as it is.
Adam, please, don't wait for me this time.
Because, honestly, I don't deserve you.
I didn't want to fall in love with him.
You kept saying, "Feel something!"
Are you happy now?
No.
I feel guilty for convincing you,
but I never thought he'd be such a liar.
-That's Tauruses for you. I even--
-I can't believe it!
I can't believe
he turned out to be such a lowlife!
Have you shed it?
No!
You'll see.
I'll crush him so hard
he won't know what hit him.
Why can't anyone understand me?
Why can't anyone understand that I'm…
I mean, I'm not after revenge.
That doesn't matter to me.
I just…
There's something…
There's this painful, horrible feeling.
I just want it to go away.
I wish I'd never listened to you
and fallen in love.
I didn't know that love hurts this much.
It hurts so much.
Yasmine, honey, love does hurt.
Love is painful.
It's also the most beautiful thing
in the world.
It'd be a shame not to experience it.
I'm "the monster"?
I don't want to see him
or talk to him ever again!
Is that him?
-Is it him?
-I don't know.
-No. It's Sama.
Hello? Hi, Sama.
I did what you told me.
I broke up with him.
Did I tell you to do that?
Well, you were right.
Thank you, Yasmine. Because…
I would've hurt Adam,
and truth is, he doesn't deserve it.
Yes, he does! He's…
What I mean is,
if you're comfortable with your decision,
then good for you. Really, well done.
How did he feel about it?
How did he take it?
He…
He got very emotional.
He got emotional?
-Go get the door!
-I want to listen.
I'll tell you later.
Yeah, Sama, dear.
Go on. What happened next?
Great!
Hi, Hala. How are you?
Is Yasmine here?
No. Yasmine isn't here.
But her car's here,
and she's not answering her phone.
I want to see her.
She's not here.
Forget Yasmine.
What are you saying?
She's my fiancée. How can I "forget her"?
Oh, really?
You're hilarious.
Sorry, excuse me.
It's just that I'm a bit confused.
Because between her and Sama,
I don't know who's your fiancée anymore.
Who's your fiancée, Adam?
You know how hard it is for Yasmine
to let anyone into her life.
She trusted you and loved you.
Why did you do that to her?
Look, you're all…
I… She's the one I love.
And you all know that, right?
I know I made a mistake.
No doubt about that.
But I did it to avoid hurting anyone.
I didn't want to hurt Yasmine.
I didn't want to hurt her.
I got tired of it myself.
I'm constantly struggling with myself,
not knowing what to do.
Please, Hala. Please, let me see her.
I know she's here.
Just ask her
to give me a chance to explain.
You didn't hurt her.
That's right.
You destroyed her.
If you don't mind, stop hurting her.
Leave, Adam.
Leave.
People come and go.
No problem.
It is a problem.
And a big one too.
Adam, you can lie to everyone,
but you can't lie to yourself.
You chose her.
The only girl you didn't want to lose--
But she's gone.
I lost her.
Your late grandma,
wouldn't she have a saying about this?
My grandma? No.
But her late mother always said
there's a solution for every problem.
But first, take a warm shower.
But, son…
I don't want Yasmine thinking I loved her
just for this contract.
Take a deep breath.
And remember,
crying isn't weakness.
On the contrary,
crying is a detox.
It clears your feelings.
Cry.
Cry now.
Yes.
Shed those tears.
Cleanse this injustice out of you.
Rid yourself of the poison.
Yes, cry.
Is the cake ready? Bring it in.
Yes, bring it in.
Why did the DJ stop the song--
Ask the DJ why he stopped the song.
Just play any--
First of all,
I'm sorry for ruining the wedding.
I'd like to congratulate the newlyweds,
and give them a piece of advice.
Love each other.
Enjoy your time together.
What's Adam doing on the stage?
-Forgive each other.
-Why isn't anyone answering?
Come here. What is Adam doing on stage?
I don't know.
You don't know?
My wedding was supposed to be
in two weeks.
I had nothing to do with it.
But because I'm a brainless idiot,
I lost the most beautiful person
in my life.
Don't be like me and lose her.
I just want to see her one more time
to tell her how much I love her,
and that my life is nothing without her.
If I had even a one percent chance
she might forgive me,
I'd…
I'd fix every mistake I made.
The song I'm about to sing,
I wrote it for her.
She's the only one who made me sing again.
So, if you don't mind,
let me dedicate this song to her.
Thank you
For all the good times
For all the memories
And I remember
When we were little
Little, little
Days would go by
And hours would fly
But today
I decided to live
The rest of my life
Without worrying
About any insecurities
To me the past is dead, dead
Thank you
For all the years
For all the nostalgia
Being apart
Doesn't exist, exist, exist
After I found you again
Yeah
I'll keep yearning and coming back to you
Oh
No one can break us apart
Let us be each other's rock
Our love shall live forever
For ever and ever and ever
Thank you
Thank you, thank you
For all the good times
Thank you
Thank you, thank you
For all the memories
I remember
When we were little
Days would go by
And hours would fly
Hours
Thank you
Thank you.
Did you think the film ends here?
Of course not!
She didn't forgive me that easily.
How could you hide this from me?
You lied to me? I trusted you!
-We argued a lot.
-I loved you!
We laughed a lot.
Yasmine! Wait! Let's talk about it!
She ran away a lot.
But eventually…
Hey, newlyweds!